<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hm Spiro App</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="login_message">Welcome to the Home Spirometry study. Please enter the password to proceed. </string>


    <string name="incorrect_password">If you do not remember the password, please contact your Enrolling Center.</string>

    <string name="spirometer_not_connected">Connection Failed\n\nPlease make sure that the Spirometor has sufficient battery and the batteries are
        properly seated.</string>

    <string name="enable_bluetooth"> Please enable bluetooth on the tablet to connect to the spirometer and proceed with the test</string>

    <string name="questionnaire_instruction">Please complete a short survey.\n\nYou will be asked whether you have any new symptoms. \n\nWhen given a single YES or NO option whether you have any of the listed symptoms, you will be presented with a YES OR NO option for each of the symptoms. Please select YES or NO for each of the symptoms. </string>

    <string name="pulse_instruction">You will be placing a pulse oximeter over either your index or middle finger for 60 seconds. The 60 seconds will begin once the device begins to record your heart rate. Please push and release the button on the pulse oximeter and press next. </string>

    <string name="q1">Do you have any of the following?\nA NEW cough, runny nose, sore throat, fever, shaking chills, muscle aches or recent diarrhea? Please choose one below.</string>

    <string name="q2">Do you have any of the following?\nA NEW cough, or cough now producing sputum/mucus, new wheezing or new shortness of breath? Please choose one below.</string>

    <string name="q3">Do you have any of the following?\nA NEW generalized weakness, lightheadedness or dizziness? Please choose one below.</string>

    <string name="q4">Do you have any of the following?\nA NEW shortness of breath at rest, on exertion or when lying flat, new shortness of breath that awakens you from sleep or new swelling in your feet or legs? Please choose one below.</string>

    <string name="ifYes"> Check each symptom that is NEW: </string>

    <string name="test_complete">Thank you. \n \n Please continue daily testing before 12PM. \n \n Please Contact (314) 747-0497 for assistance if needed.</string>

    <string name="you_will_be_contacted">Testing and Questionnaire Complete. \n \n Your Enrolling Center will contact you for follow up instructions. Please contact your Enrolling Center if you do not hear back within 4 hours.</string>
    <string name="repeat_for_4_days">Please repeat all tests and questionnaire between 6am and noon for the next 4 days.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_po3">PO3</string>

    <string name="no_alarm_set">You Currently Do Not Have Any Appointment</string>
    <string name="LoginActivity"> LoginActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>

    <!--    Help Page Strings-->
    <string name="SpirometerConnectingActivity"> SpirometerConnectingActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="BlowActivity"> BlowActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="PulseActivity"> PulseActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="ApplicationChooseActivity"> ApplicationChooseActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="NoActivityForHelp">No string found for the activity lead to this help page. Please add a string literal to the strings.xml
        file with name same as the activity name</string>
    <string name="search_for_pulse">Searching for Pulse Oximeter</string>
    <string name="pulse_not_found">The Pulse Oximeter was not found. Please ensure that the device has enough battery. Please press the button on the device and then the RETRY button below</string>
    <string name="PulseConnectingActivity"> PulseConnectingActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="pulse_direction">Please insert any finger except the thumb completely into the pulse oximeter</string>

    <string name="QuestionnaireInstructionActivity"> QuestionnaireInstructionActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>

    <string name="TestCompleteActivity"> TestCompleteActivity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="Q1Activity"> Q1Activity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="Q2Activity"> Q2Activity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="Q3Activity"> Q3Activity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="Q4Activity"> Q4Activity help page. Come back and fill this out </string>
    <string name="testingPeriodDay">1</string>
    <string name="questionSkip">Please complete all questions before continuing.</string>

    <string name="continueButton">Continue</string>
    <string name="q1Back">You are at the beginning of the questionnaire.</string>

    <string name="mode1">Pre Surveillance Mode</string>
    <string name="mode2">Surveillance Mode</string>
    <string name="mode3">Surveillance Mode</string>
    <string name="mode4">Different Study Arm</string>
    <string name="mode5">Out of Study</string>
    <string name="surveillnce_mode_instruction">Please test every Monday</string>
    <string name="presurveillnce_mode_instruction">Please test daily before 12PM </string>
    <string name="transfer_mode_title">You are transferred to Surveillance Mode</string>
    <string name="transfer_mode_message">Tests are now scheduled on Monday Mornings</string>
    <string-array name="patient_ages">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>40</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
